(
"ai_sub_version": "3.2.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-08T08:40:03.895183",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 17,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
BIRTH DAY FESTIVAL
Juice=Juice / S/mileage / Morning Musume. / Berryz Kobo / °C-ute
Morning Musume.
°C-ute
S/mileage
Juice=Juice
Berryz Kobo
Morning Musume.
Vestia Zeta
Tokoyami Towa
Aki Rosenthal
Hakui Koyori
Momosuzu Nene
Morning Musume.
愛の園～Touch My Heart!～
Garden of Love ~Touch My Heart!~
OH~ everytime, I'm so proud of you
Oh... every time, I'm so proud of you
Touch my heart and touch me please
もっと近づいて欲しい
I want you to come closer
どんなことも話して欲しいのよ
I want you to tell me everything
Touch my heart and touch me please
出来そうもないくらいなこと
Even things that seem impossible...
おねだりしてみてくれていいよ
...it's okay to ask me for them
ずっと憧れてた人と
The person I had been longing for all this time...
再会した
...I finally reunited with him
運命感じなきゃ
If I don't feel destiny...
嘘だよ
...then it's a lie
Now touch my heart
100年たって
Even if 100 years pass...
地球が変わっても
...and the Earth changes,
気持ちはかわらないわ
my feelings will not change,
愛の園
it's the Garden of Love
Now touch my heart
...の私は
...the good girl in me...
バイバイ
...will say bye-bye.
Hey! Every time
I'm so proud of you
Touch my heart! & touch me please!
もっと意地悪でいいよ
It's okay for you to be meaner.
過去も未来も
Both the past and the future...
あなたの自由でしょ！
...are your freedom, right!
Touch my heart! & touch me please!
夢は夢と言うの？
Are dreams just dreams?
あなたの夢を知りたい
I want to know your dreams.
ずっと忘れない
The nights I'll never forget...
夜が続いているわ
...are continuing.
運命抱きしめて
I'll embrace destiny...
眠るわ
...and fall asleep.
now! touch my heart
千年経って
Even if 1,000 years pass...
宇宙で暮らしても
...and we live in space,
私は変わらないわ
I won't change.
愛の園
In that garden of love.
now! touch my heart
明日になって
If tomorrow comes...
私が邪魔ならば
...and I'm in your way,
良い子の私は
the good girl in me...
バイバイ
...will say bye-bye.
Let's go!
One!
Two!
One, two, one!
now! touch my heart
千年経って
Even if 1,000 years pass...
宇宙で暮らしても
...and we live in space,
私は変わらないわ
I won't change.
愛の園
In that garden of love.
now! touch my heart
明日になって
If tomorrow comes...
私が邪魔ならば
...and I'm in your way,
良い子の私は
the good girl in me...
バイバイ
...will say bye-bye.
Hey! Every time
I'm so proud of you
キキリキー！はーい！ホロライブEnglish -Myth-の小鳥遊キアラだよ！
Kikiriki! Hi! I am Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English -Myth-!
そして、今日の私の誕生日3Dライブへようこそ！
And welcome to my birthday 3D Live today!
最初の曲は、モーニング娘。の象徴的で比較的古い曲、「愛の園」でした！
The first song was an iconic, relatively old song from Morning Musume called "Ai no Sono"!
イェーイ！気に入ってくれた？
Yay! Did you like it?
面白い動きがいくつかあって、もう私って何なんだろうって感じ！（笑）
There were some funny moves, it was just like... what am I? (laughs)
というわけでご覧の通り、今日もハロー！プロジェクトのカバー曲バースデーフェスティバルをお送りします。
So, as you can see, today, once again, I'm doing a Hello! Project cover song Birthday Festival.
ハロプロのカバー曲をテーマにしたライブをするのは、今回で2回目です。
It's my second time doing a Hello! Project cover song-themed live.
前回のライブは見てくれた？見てくれていたらいいな！
Did you watch the last one? I hope you did!
あの時、「これも絶対に歌いたい！」と思った曲がたくさんあって、だから今日ここにいるんです。
And back then, there were a bunch of songs that I felt like, "Ah, I want to do so badly!" and that's why we're here today.
だから、たくさんのハロプロ曲を楽しみにしててね。
And, yeah, so lots of Hello! Project songs to look forward to.
それと、ジャジャーン！ハッシュタグ「#KiaraBday2026」をぜひ使ってね。
Also, ta-da! #KiaraBday2026, please use it.
私を有名にして、スクリーンショットやクリップを撮って、ここで何が起きてるかネットのみんなに教えてね。
Make me famous, take some screenshots, some clips, tell the internet about this, what's happening here.
あと、この背景について少し話そうかな。これ何だろうって思ってるでしょ？
Also, let's talk a little bit about the background. What is this, you might wonder?
これまでの人生でハロプロのMVをたくさん見てきた人なら、実はピンとくるかも。これはモーニング娘。の曲のMVからインスパイアされているからです。
If you've watched a lot of Hello! Project music videos in your life, you might actually recognize this because it's from a Morning Musume song, inspired by its music video.
えーと、これから歌う曲かな？もしかしたらこの次の曲かも？
Um... maybe an upcoming song? Maybe after this?
というわけで、今日は色々なコーナーがあります。まずはこのモーニング娘。コーナーからスタートして、
So, we will have corners today. We're starting right now with the Morning Musume corner,
そのあと他のコーナーもあって、大好きなハロー！プロジェクトの各グループに捧げたコーナーになります。
and then we'll have other corners too, that are all dedicated to my favorite Hello! Project groups.
それぞれのコーナーには、これみたいにそのグループを象徴する背景幕が用意されています。
And for each corner, there will be like a representative backdrop, like this one.
だから、今日のステージのいろんなバリエーションに注目してね！ね？
So, please pay attention to the different variations of the stages today! Hm? Hm?
それでね、今は一人で踊ったからちょっと寂しいな。誰か友達が来てパフォーマンスを手伝ってほしいな。
And now, I'm kind of sad because I danced alone. I want some friends to come and help me perform.
それじゃあ、始めて次の曲へ進みましょうか？
So, shall we begin and continue with the next song?
イエス、イエス、イエス！みんな、おいでー！
Yes, yes, yes! Bring in the ladies!
かも かも かも かも
Maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe...
笑った顔をして返事した
I replied with a smile on my face,
あなたがウソを付く合図だね
but that's your sign for telling a lie.
二年目の記念を前にして
Right before our second anniversary,
わたしが振られちゃって終わるのね
I'm getting dumped, and it's all over.
「また 一人ぼっち マリコ」
"All alone again, Mariko..."
自分に 言い聞かす 私
I keep telling myself.
気付かないフリをしていつまでも
Pretending not to notice, I wonder if
抱きしめられていようかな
I should just let you hold me forever.
あぁ あなたが優しいのは
Ah, I know that you are kind,
わかってる けど その分つらすぎるの
but that only makes it so much more painful.
お祈りをしたけれど
Although I prayed,
心は遠く離れてゆく
our hearts are only drifting further apart.
あぁ 私からお別れ告げようと
Ah, I thought I'd say goodbye first,
そう 思ったけど出来ない
yes, I thought so, but I can't do it.
会話の中で何度も
So many times during our conversation,
タイミングみてたけど
I kept waiting for the right moment, but...
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry,
I might cry...
かも
Maybe,
maybe,
かも
maybe.
どうしてそんな風に無理するの
Why do you force yourself like that?
嫌ならお別れを言ってよね
If you don't want this, just say goodbye.
ちょっとはワガママも言ってみたけど
I tried being a little selfish,
優しく笑顔で答える人
but you just answer with a gentle smile.
「もう これでいいの マリコ」
"Is this really okay, Mariko?"
自問自答する 私
I ask myself over and over.
最後だって言う前に抱きしめて
Before you say it's the end, hold me tight,
ねぇ 冷たくていいから
hey, even if your embrace is cold.
そう あなたの優しさが罪なのよ
Yes, your kindness is a sin.
ほら 決心が鈍くなる
See? My determination is wavering.
出会った頃みたいに
Just like when we first met,
毎日確かめ合いたい
I want us to reassure each other every day.
あぁ もう少しこのままいたいけど
Ah, I want to stay like this a little longer,
そう あなたといたいけれど
yes, I want to be with you, but...
最後の夜が来たら
If our final night arrives,
強気のフリしながら
while pretending to be strong...
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry,
I might cry...
かも
Maybe,
maybe,
かも
maybe.
そう あなたの優しさが罪なのよ
Yes, your kindness is a sin.
ほら 決心が鈍くなる
See? My determination is wavering.
出会った頃みたいに
Just like when we first met,
毎日確かめ合いたい
I want us to reassure each other every day.
あぁ もう少しこのままいたいけど
Ah, I want to stay like this a little longer,
そう あなたといたいけれど
yes, I want to be with you, but...
最後の夜が来たら
If our final night arrives,
強気のフリしながら
while pretending to be strong...
泣いちゃうかも
I might cry,
I might cry...
かも
Maybe,
maybe,
かも
maybe.
はやく
Hurry up...
会いたいよ
I want to see you.
ねえ
Hey...
はやく
hurry...
あなたに会いたい
I want to see you.
へや
Hey ya!
超えよう
Let's cross over!
へや
Hey ya!
超えよう
Let's cross over!
Oh...
ヘイヤ ホエオ
Hey ya, ho e oh
先にむかってる ROAD
The road ahead...
止まらないミュージック
...and the music that won't stop.
恋人からの花束
A bouquet of flowers from my lover,
真夜中届くメール
and a message that arrives at midnight.
女の子なら 誰でも思う
Every girl dreams of...
HAPPY END STORY
...a happy end story,
...a happy end story.
やさしくされりゃ うれしいけど
I'm happy when you're kind,
限りなく求めちゃう
but I'll always want more.
色っぽい キューピット
A sexy cupid...
じれったい キスもっと
...and an impatient kiss, give me more.
熱い鼓動の SEXY ISLAND
With a racing heartbeat on this sexy island.
笑ってる星も
Even the smiling stars,
気取ってる子供も
and the kids acting all grown up...
この愛を見届けてほしい
...I want them to witness this love.
欲しい
I want it so much.
ヘイヤ ホエオ
Hey ya, ho e oh
海が輝いて JEALOUSY
The sea shines with jealousy.
ひとりごとの週末
A weekend of talking to myself.
あなたと来れたら 嬉しい
I'd be so happy if I could come with you.
不思議なニオイに クンクン
Sniffing at a mysterious scent.
寂しい夜と
A lonely night...
楽しい1時間
...and one fun hour.
HAPPY END STORY
A happy end story,
a happy end story.
もう一度言うわ
I'll say it once more:
大好きです
I love you.
抱きしめて 離さないで
Hold me tight and never let me go.
色っぽい ビスケット
A sexy biscuit...
じれったい 秘密もっと
...and an impatient secret, tell me more.
ずっと続くの SEXY ISLAND
It will go on forever on this sexy island.
愛して 急接近
Love me, drawing rapidly closer.
未来に 大接近
To the future, making a grand approach.
どこまでも抱きしめて
Hold me close, no matter how far.
欲しい
I want it so much.
色っぽい キューピット
A sexy cupid...
じれったい キスもっと
...and an impatient kiss, give me more.
熱い鼓動の SEXY ISLAND
With a racing heartbeat on this sexy island.
笑ってる星も
Even the smiling stars,
気気取ってる子供も
and the kids acting all grown up...
この愛を見届けてほしい
...I want them to witness this love.
欲しい
I want it so much.
色っぽい ビスケット
A sexy biscuit...
じれったい 秘密もっと
...and an impatient secret, tell me more.
ずっと続くの SEXY ISLAND
It will go on forever on this sexy island.
愛して 急接近
Love me, drawing rapidly closer.
未来に 大接近
To the future, making a grand approach.
どこまでも抱きしめて
Hold me close, no matter how far.
欲しい
I want it so much.
ヘイヤ ホエオ
Hey ya, ho e oh
Oh...
°C-ute
Isaki Riona
Koganei Niko
Mizumiya Su
Rindo Chihaya
Kikirara Vivi
渋谷を歩く
Walking through Shibuya,
一人で歩く
walking all alone,
人混みの中
in the middle of the crowd.
言い過ぎな あの人探す
I look for that person who says too much.
手をつないでいい？ その思いから
Can we hold hands? From that feeling...
もっと育んでみたいだけなの
I just want to nurture it some more.
あの人を こんな私を
That person... someone like me...
どうか離さないでね
Please, don't let me go.
恋する思いが MY DIARY
My diary of loving thoughts...
大きく膨らみ I LOVE YOU
Expands so big, I love you.
考えすぎたら MY DIARY
If I think too much, my diary...
空回りしちゃうの
Will just spin its wheels.
まだまだ私は MY DIARY
I'm still, my diary...
あなたが怖いわ I LOVE YOU
Afraid of you, I love you.
きっといつの日か MY DIARY
Surely, someday, my diary...
嫌われちゃいそうで ああ
I feel like you might hate me, ah...
あなたを見つけ 涙出ちゃった
I found you, and tears came out.
少し前から
From a little while ago...
私に気づいていたらなんて
Thinking, "What if you'd noticed me?"
少しズルいよ だけど言えない
You're a little unfair, but I can't say it.
最初のキッカケは私だし
Because the first spark came from me.
お熱よ うつむいてたら
I'm crazy for you, when I was looking down...
手を握ってくれたわ
You held my hand.
おとなになっても MY DIARY
Even when I grow up, my diary...
もっとその先も I LOVE YOU
Even further beyond, I love you.
腰が曲がっても MY DIARY
Even when our backs are bent with age, my diary...
手をつなぐ時には
When we hold hands...
ドキドキするでしょ MY DIARY
Your heart will race, right? My diary...
恥ずかしいでしょ I LOVE YOU
It'll be embarrassing, right? I love you.
それでも私を MY DIARY
Even so, my diary...
優しく包んでね ああ
Please wrap me in your kindness, ah...
おとなになっても MY DIARY
Even when I grow up, my diary...
もっとその先も I LOVE YOU
Even further beyond, I love you.
腰が曲がっても MY DIARY
Even when our backs are bent with age, my diary...
手をつなぐ時には
When we hold hands...
ドキドキするでしょ MY DIARY
Your heart will race, right? My diary...
恥ずかしいでしょ I LOVE YOU
It'll be embarrassing, right? I love you.
それでも私を MY DIARY
Even so, my diary...
優しく包んでね ああ
Please wrap me in your kindness, ah...
[Song: 涙の色]
[Song: Color of Tears (Namida no Iro)]
友情 あなたは友情 分からず屋のままね
Friendship, you are "friendship", still stubborn as ever.
もう付き合いきれない さよなら愛しい人
I can't deal with you anymore, goodbye my beloved.
友情 友達なんて 戻れるわけないでしょ
Friendship, there's no way we can go back to being just friends, right?
困らせたいの 我が儘に 振り回すつもり
I want to trouble you, and selfishly throw you around.
浮気なら それなりに 許すつもりだった
If it was a fling, I was intending to forgive you in my own way.
プライドを 傷つけた あの日は許せない
But I can't forgive that day you hurt my pride.
涙 とまらぬ涙 これでスッキリするわ
Tears, non-stop tears, with this I'll feel refreshed.
あなたを信じてた あの日がもったいない
Believing in you, that day was such a waste.
愛してた
...I loved you.
あー
Ah...
そいでも愛してた
Even so, I loved you.
あなたとのサヨナラ
Saying goodbye to you...
どうよ
How is it?
心の隙間
The gap in my heart...
風を引きそうだけど
It feels like I'm catching a cold,
それならすぐ治るし
but that will heal soon.
サヨナラ 愛しい人
Goodbye, my beloved.
薄情
Heartless...
と言われても
Even if you call me that,
ヨリを戻したりしないから
I won't get back together with you.
もう電話は出ないわ
I won't answer your calls anymore,
どんなに寂しくても
no matter how lonely I feel.
いつもより早いけど
It's earlier than usual, but
ベッドに入るわ
I'm going to bed.
懐かしい記憶と
It's time to fight
戦う時間 あー
with my nostalgic memories, ah...
涙 思い出 涙
Tears, memories, tears.
悲しくなんかないよ
I'm not sad at all.
私ももう大人ね
I'm already an adult, too.
今頃そう思うわ
That's what I think now, ah...
あんなに愛してた
I loved you so much,
あなたとのサヨナラ
my goodbye with you.
涙 とまらない 涙
Tears, unstoppable tears.
これでスッキリするわ
This will make me feel refreshed.
あなたを信じてた
I believed in you,
あの日がもったいない
that day was such a waste, ah...
涙 思い出 涙
Tears, memories, tears.
悲しくなんかないよ
I'm not sad at all.
私ももう大人ね
I'm already an adult, too.
今頃そう思うわ
That's what I think now, ah...
あんなに愛してた
I loved you so much,
あなたとのサヨナラ
my goodbye with you.
あんなに愛してた
I loved you so much,
あなたとのサヨナラ
my goodbye with you.
イェーイ！
Yeah! Woo!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
ようこそ、ようこそ！
Welcome, welcome!
イェーイ！
Yay!
That was "Forever Love" and "Namida no Iro" with Flow Glow!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
すげえ！なんかFlow Glowのメンバーになった気分！
Amazing! It's like I'm a member of Flow Glow!
いや、めっちゃ嬉しいです！こんなに大人数で、うん、踊れて！
No, I'm really so happy to dance in a big group like this!
まずは自己紹介をみんなに、英語でやってもらおうかな！
First, I'd like everyone to introduce themselves in English!
えー！英語で？！
What?! In English?!
やばい！できるかな？
Oh no! Can we do it?
インターナショナル！がんばる！
International! I'll do my best!
順番はお任せしますけど...
I'll leave the order up to you...
いつもの順番で！オッケー！
In the usual order! Okay!
Hello everyone! My name is Riona. I'm Flow Glow leader, Riona! Yay! Nice to meet you!
おおー！完璧！
Ohh! Perfect!
あー！
Ah!
にこたん、かおひー！
Niko-tan, Kao-hi!
My name is Koganei Niko! Flow Glow's comedian modoki. Yeah!
Modoki? 英語がちょっと足りないけど...
Comedian-ish? Her English is a bit lacking, but...
はい、しゅぴしゅわー！We are Mizumiya Suo! Yay!
Yes, Shupi Shuwa! We are Mizumiya Suo! Yay!
We are? (笑)
"We are"? (laughs)
PR担当！PR担当！
PR representative! PR representative!
Suo-chan, 日本語の「大きい」は英語で「small」？
Suo-chan, is Japanese "ookii" (big) "small" in English?
No, no... Yes! Yes!
Classmate, thank you! Not, not... Kiara-senpai!
さすがに分かったか？さすがさすが！
I guess she understood that! As expected!
はい、次！
Okay, next!
Hi! Flow Glow's DJ and driver, Rindo Chiyo!
お疲れ様でした！
Great work, everyone!
プロログお疲れ様！
Great job, Prolog!
おー！
Oh!
ビーフ？
Beef?
ピンクビーフ！ピンクビーフ！
Pink beef! Pink beef!
はい、せーの、うー、プロログ！
Alright, ready, go... Prolog!
イェーイ！
Yay!
うー、アイムスゲヨ、キキララ、ビビって！
Woo, I'm Sugesyo, Kikirara, Bibitte!
すげー！
So cool!
すげよ！すげよ！
Incredible! Incredible!
イェーイ！
Yay!
Well, uh, when I chose to do these songs,
I really wanted to bring in Prolog because I know they're all really good at dancing.
Yeah, and performing! みんないつも上手だから、絶対プロログ誘おうと、完成度高いと思って。
Yeah, and performing! Since everyone is so good, I knew I had to invite Prolog, thinking the quality would be high.
でも、なんか困ったこととか、難しかったフリとか、なんかありましたか？
But, did you have any troubles, or was there any difficult choreography?
全部！
Everything!
全部難しかった！
Everything was difficult!
え、でもカッコよかった！みんな、なんか揃ったの見た時に、めっちゃカッコいい！ってなりました。
But it was so cool! When I saw you all in sync, I thought, "That's so cool!"
私も、なんかそのみんなで、どんどん出来上がって、完成度が高くなっていくうちに、
Me too! As we practiced and the quality got higher and higher,
もう幸せすぎて！
I was just so happy!
すごいカッコいいって言ってくれてて嬉しかった。
I was so happy you said it was so cool.
なんか、カノンって結構、交互のフリみたいな...
Like, in Kanon, there's a lot of alternating choreography...
そうそう、こういうのね！
Right, like this!
そういうの、今まであんまりなかったから、キアラ先輩にね、呼んでもらって、それが出来て嬉しかったです！
We didn't really have that kind of thing before, so I was happy Kiara-senpai invited us and we could do it!
嬉しかったー！
We were so happy!
そうだね、なんかあの、順番で回るとか、結構多くて、大変でした。
Right, like rotating in order, there was quite a lot of that, so it was hard.
まあ、すいません、難しいフリして。あの、みなさんのコーナー？
Well, sorry for the difficult choreography. Um, your corner?
キュートのコーナーがあって、キュートっていうグループは、ダンスがマジでいつも難しいです。
There was a Cute corner, and the group Cute's dance is always really difficult.
確かに！実力派。
True! They are highly skilled.
ごめんね、でもみんなよく出来てた！
Sorry about that, but everyone did so well!
めっちゃ楽しかった！ありがとうございます。
It was so much fun! Thank you so much.
キュートと言えば、I want to know everybody's like, favorite Hello! Project song?
Speaking of Cute, I want to know everybody's like, favorite Hello! Project song?
ハロプロの好きな曲！知りたいけど、じゃあまず、すーちゃんありますか？
Your favorite Hello! Project songs! I want to know, but first, Su-chan, do you have one?
「アモレ」！「アモレ」！
"Amore"! "Amore"!
おー！アモレ！アモレ大好き！
Oh! Amore! I love Amore!
おー、良い。結構最近の曲ですね！良いですね。
Oh, nice. That's a pretty recent song! Nice.
あと、にこちゃんは？
Also, Niko-chan?
にこちゃん、「バカヤロー」！「バカヤロー...」大好きです！
Niko-chan, "Bakayarou"! I love "Bakayarou..."!
大好き！良いよね！すごく良いよね！
I love it! It's good, right! It's really good!
分かる！と、結構ヲタクと聞いて...
I get it! I heard you're quite a big fan...
そうです！えっと、そう、私の好きな曲は、モーニング娘。'14さんの「時空を超え 宇宙を超え」
Yes! Um, yes, my favorite song is Morning Musume '14's "Toki wo Koe Sora wo Koe".
あ、それやるやつ！名曲ですね。
Oh, the one we're doing! It's a masterpiece.
「時空を超え 宇宙を超え」ってすごい、カッコいい、しっとりした曲。
"Toki wo Koe Sora wo Koe" is a really cool, beautiful song.
良いですね！でも、私は天邪鬼（あまのじゃく）もすごく好きです。
It's nice! But, I also really like "Amanojaku".
天邪鬼！天邪鬼は、去年にやってたんです。
Amanojaku! We did "Amanojaku" last year.
天邪鬼大好きです！
I love Amanojaku!
なるほど、おー、詳しそうですね！ヲタクだね。
I see, wow, you seem to know a lot! A real fan.
はーちゃんはどの曲が？
Ha-chan, which song?
私は、「ソラシド〜ねえねえ〜」が、初めて聴いた時にめっちゃ素敵な曲だなと思って、大好きです！
For me, "Solasido ~Nee Nee~", when I first heard it, I thought it was such a wonderful song, and I love it!
Buono!ですね。それも、Buono!大好きです。
Buono! indeed. We all love Buono!.
みんな大好きなBuono!ですね。
Everyone's favorite, Buono!.
分かる！と、びびわんは？
I get it! And, Bibi-one?
はい！びびわんは、「チュッ！チュッ！チュッ！サマーパーティ」！
Yes! Bibi-one is "Chu! Chu! Chu! Summer Party"!
キアラ先輩に、チュッチュしてほしいです！チュッチュッチュッ...
I want Kiara-senpai to blow me kisses! Chu chu chu...
やめてー！
Stop it!
キアラ先輩、騙されないでください！騙されてないよ！
Kiara-senpai, don't be fooled! I'm not fooled!
可愛い！
So cute!
でも、この色んな曲名を聞くだけで、このライブ、ハロプロカバーソングライブ、何度も何度もやりたいですけど、
But, just hearing all these song titles makes me want to do this Hello! Project cover song live over and over again,
とりあえずは、あの、まだまだあります！
but for now, um, there's still more to come!
キュートの次に、他のパートも、他のグループもありますので、
After Cute, there are other parts and other groups,
次のパートに行きましょう！プロログのみんな、ありがとう！
so let's go to the next part! Thank you, everyone from Prolog!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
というわけで、Let's go to the next corner!
With that, let's go to the next corner!
イェーイ！
Yay!
S/mileage
[Group: S/mileage]
犬神ころね
[Member: Inugami Korone]
兎田ぺこら
[Member: Usada Pekora]
ワトソン・アメリア
[Member: Watson Amelia]
S/mileage
[Group: S/mileage]
有頂天LOVE
[Song: Uchouten LOVE]
いま片付けないような
These sparkling days...
キラキラした毎日
...that I can't put away just yet.
ぶっちゃけ噂になってる
To be honest, I'm living days...
日々を送ってる
...that are the talk of the town!
恋をしたら勉強が
When you fall in love,
手につかない毎日
you can't focus on studying at all.
恋のせいにしちゃってさ
So let's just blame it all on love!
今日だって カレと登校中に
Even today, on my way to school with him,
待ち合わせてるの
we arranged to meet up.
チョーカーを少し変えたこと
I wonder if you'll notice...
気づくかしら キミは
...that I changed my choker slightly.
わわわわ
Wa-wa-wa-wa!
ダッダッダッダッ 脱出不可能なほど
Da-da-da-da! To the point of no escape...
恋をしちゃっているわ
...I've fallen so deeply in love!
大好きが止まらない
I can't stop loving you!
Oh Lovey-Dovey-Dovey-Dovey Lovey-Dovey-Dovey-Dovey Love Me Do!
わわわわ
Wa-wa-wa-wa!
ダッダッダッダッ 卒倒するほど
Da-da-da-da! To the point of swooning...
時代を変えるわ
...we're going to change the era!
スポットライトを浴びる二人
The two of us bathed in the spotlight...
口づけをしましょう
...let's share a kiss.
有頂天LOVE
Ecstatic LOVE!
夢見る 15歳
[Song: Yumemiru Fifteen]
女の子には
For girls,
秘密の恋のボタンがあるのよ
there's a secret love button, you know!
今年の夏は負けない
I won't lose this summer.
去年みたいに弱気じゃない
I'm not timid like I was last year!
あぁ
Ah...
THE Summer Love 胸が騒ぐわ
...THE Summer Love! My heart is pounding!
THE Summer Love
実際 恋するだけなら誰でもできる
Actually, anyone can just fall in love...
勇気を持ってたたかわなきゃ
...you've got to have courage and fight!
実際 恋愛するのって大変に
Actually, being in a relationship is extremely...
見逃せない
...and I can't miss out on it!
夏祭り 手を繋ぎ
Holding hands at a summer festival,
花火を見上げて
looking up at the fireworks...
キレイだと 私を見て
"You're beautiful," looking at me...
キミが言う
...that's what you'll say.
浴衣着て 金魚すくい
Wearing a yukata, scooping goldfish...
キミがさらっと 3匹で
...and you smoothly catch three!
なんて恋 夢見てる
That's the kind of love I dream of...
15才
...at fifteen.
一人きり イヤフォンで
All alone with my earphones in,
音楽 聞いている
I'm listening to music.
意味もなく 涙とか
For no reason at all, tears...
出てきちゃう
...just start to fall.
寂しいよ 寂しいよ
I'm lonely, I'm lonely.
なぜだか 寂しいよ
For some reason, I feel so lonely.
すごい恋 夢見てる
Dreaming of a wonderful love...
15才
...at fifteen.
Summer Love
Juice=Juice
Kobo Kanaeru
Pavolia Reine
ついてくる気が
Do you have any intention...
あるんでしょうか
...of following me?
ねえ 君は
Hey, what about you?
オドオドしてちゃ
If you're acting so timid,
飲み込まれるよ
you'll get swallowed up.
都会では
In the big city.
愛だ恋だのと
If you intend to speak...
言うつもりなら
...of love and romance,
そうね 君
That's right, you must...
男らしくて
...be manly...
自信ありげで
...and confident,
爽やかに
...and refreshing.
私だって そりゃね保存
Of course, I want...
甘えたいと思う
...to act spoiled, too.
だけど甘い顔は
But I'm in no position...
出来ない立場なの
...to show a sweet side.
胸元のあいた服を着た私の
Notice the signal from me,
サインに気づいて
wearing clothes showing off my cleavage,
ねえ
Hey!
愛してよ
Love me!
誰にも負けず 愛して 愛して 愛しすぎて!
Love me more than anyone, love me, love me, I love you so much!
安心感 優越感 それが欲しいの
A sense of security and superiority, that's what I want.
抱きしめて
Embrace me!
生まれたまんまの 裸の裸の裸のKISS
The naked, naked, naked KISS just as we were born.
この愛が 本物と
If this love is real,
別れはいいの
I don't care if we part.
この愛が本物と 分かるように
So that I know this love is real...
KISSして
...kiss me.
愛してよ
Love me!
もう狂うほど 愛して 愛して 愛しすぎて!
Love me enough to go crazy, love me, love me, I love you so much!
少しぐらい 強引で
Being a little pushy...
ちょうどいいのよ
...is just right.
抱きしめて
Embrace me!
生まれたまんまの 裸の裸の裸のKISS
The naked, naked, naked KISS just as we were born.
この愛が 本物と
If this love is real,
別れはいいの
I don't care if we part.
この愛が本物と 分かるように
So that I know this love is real...
KISSして
...kiss me.
盛れ! ミ・アモーレ
Glam up! Mi amore!
盛れ!
Glam up!
盛れ! ミ・アモーレ
Glam up! Mi amore!
盛れ!
Glam up!
盛れ! 盛れ! 盛れ! 盛れ! 盛れ! 盛れ! 盛れ!
Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up! Glam up!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, mi amore!
一番の私を見て
Look at me at my absolute best.
ありのままなんて 愛してあげない
I won't love you just as you are.
火花みたいな 今を
For this spark-like present moment...
盛れ!
...glam up!
Glam up!
盛れ! 盛れ! 盛れ! 盛れ! 盛れ!
Glam up, glam up, glam up, glam up, glam up!
あなたの瞳はフィルター
Your eyes are a filter.
燃えてゆく恋は刹那
A burning love is only momentary.
お守りなら 綺麗なまま
If it's a charm, keeping it pristine...
笑って いられないの
...won't keep me smiling.
泣いて
Cry...
愛称も愛称も一瞬
My sweet friendliness is also just for a moment.
素顔のほうが嘘
A bare face is more of a lie.
解けた髪と甘い香りこそ 盛りの秘訣
Loose hair and sweet scent are the secrets to glamming up.
今度は私の角度で
This time, from my angle,
悪魔でも味方につける
I'll even win over the devil to my side.
美しさのレシピを
Engrave this recipe of beauty...
焼き付けて
...into your eyes.
油断できないわ
We can't afford...
私達は
...to let our guard down.
アモーレ
Amore!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, mi amore!
私を好きでいさせて
Let me keep loving you!
ありのままなんて 残したくない
I don't want to leave things just as they are.
現実以上でいたいの
I want to be more than reality.
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, mi amore!
一番の私を見て
Look at me at my absolute best.
ありのままなんて 愛してあげない
I won't love you just as you are.
火花みたいな 今を
For this spark-like present moment...
盛れ!
...glam up!
盛れ! 盛れ!
Glam up! Glam up!
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, mi amore!
あなたを好きでいさせて
Let me keep loving you!
愛しているからと 求められたら
If you ask me because you love me,
ひきにしないわ
I won't play favorites...
誰だって
...with anyone.
アモーレ ミ・アモーレ
Amore, mi amore!
私の元を去るだなんて
Leaving my side like that...
悲しい嘘だって 後味が悪い
Even if it's a sad lie, it leaves a bad aftertaste.
めちゃくちゃにして 離そう
Let's make a mess of it and part ways!
盛れ! 盛れ! 盛れ! 盛れ! 盛れ!
Glam up, glam up, glam up, glam up, glam up!
ライ ライ ライ...
Lai lai lai...
Lai, lai, lai, lai...
M-O-R-E, M-O-R-E!
Ah, more!
Berryz Kobo
Hakos Baelz
Gigi Murin
Cecilia Immergreen
Raora Panthera
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
今夜は会えそうにないやいやい
Doesn't look like I'll be able to see you tonight, yai yai...
不思議と寂しいやいやい
It's strangely lonely, yai yai...
背伸びをしてるわけじゃないのに胸が痛い
I'm not trying to act older than I am, but even so my heart aches.
仲間が集まってガキあつかい
When you're with your friends, you treat me like a kid.
今すぐ大人になりたいやい
I want to grow up quickly, yai!
こんなに苦しいのが初恋ですか？
Is first love supposed to be this painful?
アーケード
Through the arcade...
走り抜け
...I run through...
信号が青になる
...and the traffic light turns green.
あの人が
That special person...
この時間
...at this time...
ココを通る
...will pass by here.
ほら 春紅のスカーレット
Look, spring scarlet!
我慢なんてできない
I can't be patient anymore.
胸さわぎスカーレット
Scarlet premonition,
恋の色がか・お・る
the color of love is so fragrant.
Yes My Love
週末はみんなわいやいやい
On the weekend, we all get together, yai yai...
なぜなのあなたいないやいやい
...but for some reason, you're not here, yai yai.
こんな日はつまらない
Days like this are so boring.
そろそろ帰ろうかな...
I guess I should go home soon...
噂じゃ彼女ができたとか
Rumors say you've got a girlfriend,
そんなのまったく聞きたくない
but I don't want to hear a single word of it!
張り裂けそうなぐらい頭がナナメ
My head's all twisted, like it's about to burst.
雨が降る
The rain is falling...
週末は
...on this weekend...
少し街も静か
...making the streets a little quiet.
このままじゃ
At this rate...
眠れない
...I won't be able to sleep...
せつなすぎる
...it's just too bittersweet.
ah 春紅のスカーレット
Ah, spring scarlet!
そっと近づきたい
I just want to get closer to you.
胸さわぎスカーレット
Scarlet premonition,
恋の虹がひ・か・る
love's rainbow is shining bright.
Yes My Love
ほら 春紅のスカーレット
Look, spring scarlet!
我慢なんてできない
I can't be patient anymore.
胸さわぎスカーレット
Scarlet premonition,
恋の色がか・お・る
the color of love is so fragrant.
Yes My Love
ah 春紅のスカーレット
Ah, spring scarlet!
そっと近づきたい
I just want to get closer to you.
胸さわぎスカーレット
Scarlet premonition,
恋の虹がひ・か・る
love's rainbow is shining bright.
Yes My Love
Woo!
Here we go!
Yeah!
Oh my God!
Welcome back!
Hi!
Kiara, Happy Birthday!
Thank you!
It's not just my birthday, but it's another celebration
because this is the first time we're together as just two...
...dancing!
What an occasion!
How we have come to this occasion, you will never know, but please introduce yourself.
What's up? I am Chaos, the concept of,
and a steward trapped in a cage of vice, your best friend,
Hakos Baelz from Hololive English -Promise-. Witness me!
And such a good introduction!
Wow, I wish I had such an introduction!
Well, welcome, welcome, welcome. How did you like the song?
It was so hard! - Yeah, really?
Our first idol dances, this... - This is so hard!
Yes, yes, that happens often in Hello! Project, but... - I don't understand this.
But this, I remember in the dance lessons, you told me about the different genres of dance that appeared in this.
Yeah, I was quite surprised. There was a lot of house. This is quite house...
This is house? - House, okay.
And then there's also, there's locking. - Oh, this? You said that's rock?
This is locking. - Lock, locking? Locking.
Oh, you meant locking, not rocking? - No, locking!
Oh! I thought that was a rock dance style. Okay. - No, locking. Misunderstanding.
Yeah! That was so hard!
I swear! I was so surprised, I was like, "What kind of idol dance has house and locking in the same dance?" That's crazy.
They were trying all kinds of things back then, but yeah, that's from my favorite idol group, Berryz Kobo.
And it's like a pretty old song at this point, but it has one part in the choreography...
...that I thought would be perfect for like a duo. So I thought, "I want to do it with you, together!"
Is this part? (Humming)
That was so much fun!
I really wanted to do it, thank you! - Thank you!
Okay, um, I have also prepared a little game for us.
A game? - A game of... - Camera rules!
There's so many cameras, and I would like to make use of it.
We'll play a game where you have to find the camera.
Is this the first camera that we're looking for, so far? Maybe it's like here...
...uh... yeah!
Hi! - Hi! I see, I see, I see! Yay!
Okay, Bae, you find the next one. Where is that?
Is it there, or is it the opposite?
Oh, wait! Oh, I found it first! - No, what's, what's...
...where is it? - Where is it? - Oh? Are? Are? Are?
If we continue running around, surely we'll find it eventually.
Wait, hold on. - Right there!
Wait, wait, wait, up. - I see it, right there!
Hello! - Hi!
That was really difficult. - Next camera! - Where is...
...it?
Where did they find these cameras?
I see you!
When is this angle ever being used? - I see!
Hi! - Konnichiwa!
One more, one more, one more! - One more.
Under the disco ball? Wait, I saw the shadow.
Wait, the disco ball should be like...
Oh! Ah!
No. - No, it's like... - No, it's not there.
No, it's like, oh, it's hard to... - Am I looking at it?
Oh!
Yeah! - Okay, okay, okay.
Wait, one, one last-o? - Last-o? Last one.
Is that the last one? - Well, this one's easy because...
That's not a challenge!
Hi! - Yay!
Okay, okay, okay, that was fun!
Well, well, well, well, this is not the end, though.
No, no, no. What are we doing next?
Well, first of all, the Berryz Kobo corner will continue for one more song, because I love them so much.
Oh, oh! - And for the next one, I have four guests.
Four?! - And they are none other than Justice.
Because last year, for the Easter Hello! Project cover song live, I also had them over, but they were in 2D, like in a paper form.
Oh! - So I thought, well, this year, I'll get them all in 3D! - 3D! Justice!
Yeah! And they will be wearing a little bit of a costume.
A cosplay? - Cosplay, oh! - Something like that. - Costume play?
Cosplay that matches the music video.
So, pay attention to what's different.
And with that, I guess, have fun with the rest of the show...
...and the next song, which is, se-no...
Seishun Bus Guide!
今日でサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
Goodbye today, my chest hurts...
手紙書いていいんだろう？
Can I write you a letter?
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Youth Bus Guide, you are dazzling.
記念に写真とっていいかい？
Can I take a photo as a memento?
いいかい？
Can I?
一目ぼれなんだ 僕がはじけた
It was love at first sight, I burst forth.
とまらない感覚...
This unstoppable sensation...
これが恋だろう
Is this love?
君とすれ違う いいにおいがした
I passed by you and you smelled so sweet.
みんなに優しくするなよ
Don't be so kind to everyone else!
独り占めしたいんだ
I want to keep you all to myself...
その声 その笑顔 全部
That voice, that smile, all of it.
目線が合うたびしびれるよ
Every time our eyes meet, I feel a thrill.
独り占めしたいんだ
I want to keep you all to myself!
だけどサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
But goodbye, my chest hurts...
もっと話していたい
I want to talk to you more.
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Youth Bus Guide, you are dazzling.
マイクに生まれ変わりたい
I want to be reborn as your microphone.
あいつも
That guy too...
ライバル
...is a rival.
話しかけてる
He is talking to you!
湧き起こる感覚...
This sensation welling up...
これがジェラシー
...is this jealousy?
休憩時間に
During break time...
少し会話できた
...we managed to talk a little.
まつげがとても長いんだね
Your eyelashes are so long.
時間よ戻ってくれ
Time, please turn back...
最初の日にもどりたい
I want to go back to the first day.
君に伝えたいことばかり保存
There are so many things I want to tell you.
時間よ戻ってくれ
Time, please turn back!
独り占めしたいんだ保存
I want to keep you all to myself...
その声 その笑顔 全部
That voice, that smile, all of it.
目線が合うたびしびれるよ
Every time our eyes meet, I feel a thrill.
独り占めしたいんだ
I want to keep you all to myself!
今日でサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
Goodbye today, my chest hurts...
手紙書いていいんだろう？
Can I write you a letter?
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Youth Bus Guide, you are dazzling.
記念に写真とっていいかい？
Can I take a photo as a memento?
だけどサヨナラ 胸が苦しい
But goodbye, my chest hurts...
もっと話していたい
I want to talk to you more.
青春バスガイド 君はまぶしい
Youth Bus Guide, you are dazzling.
もう一度君に会いたいよ
I want to see you once more.
スッ！
Sp-
ペッ！
-ec-
スッペシャル！
-ial...
ジェネレーション！
...Generation!
どうしたらこうたら
This way or that way,
言い訳してる
you keep making excuses.
いらいら来るな
It's so irritating!
あの子がいいなら保存
If you prefer that girl,
そっち行けばいいじゃん
then why don't you just go to her?
ちゃらちゃらちゃらちゃら
Clank, clank, clank, clank,
シルバーをつけて
wearing silver accessories,
ふらふらしてる
wandering around aimlessly.
誰にアピールしてる？
Who are you trying to appeal to?
よそ見なんて許さないわよ
I won't let you look at anyone else!
好きと好きと言いなさい
Say "I love you, I love you!"
さあ
Now,
この場所で
at this place!
スッペシャル ジェネレーション
Special Generation!
運命も信じたい
I want to believe in fate.
100万年過ぎたって
Even if a million years pass by,
この愛は揺るぎない
this love will never waver.
スッペシャル ジェネレーション
Special Generation!
嫌いにはなれないわ
I can't bring myself to hate you.
直通つなぐ仲だって
Even though we have a direct connection...
昨日よりも
More than yesterday,
愛して
love me.
あだら あだら どこに行くでも
Adara, adara, wherever we go...
だらだらしている
we're just slacking off.
私が決めなきゃ
If I don't decide,
何も始まんない
nothing will start!
押したり引いたり
Pushing and pulling...
なんて器用にすることできない
is not something I can do skillfully.
まっすぐ行くだけ
I can only go straight forward!
誰しも 彼しも 驚くような
To make everyone and anyone surprised...
熱い愛で私、私だけ 抱きしめて
Hold me, only me, with your hot love!
Hold on my love!
スッペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special Generation LOVE!
孤独なことなんて感じない
I don't feel lonely at all.
いけふくろう 過ぎたって
Even if we pass the Ikebukuro owl...
この愛は 永遠
this love is eternal!
スッペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special Generation LOVE!
離れない 離さない
I won't leave you, I won't let you go.
昨日よりも 今よりも
More than yesterday, more than today,
また明日も 愛して
love me again tomorrow!
スッペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special Generation LOVE!
孤独なことなんて感じない
I don't feel lonely at all.
いけふくろう 過ぎたって
Even if we pass the Ikebukuro owl...
この愛は 永遠
this love is eternal!
スッペシャル ジェネレーション LOVE
Special Generation LOVE!
離れない 離さない
I won't leave you, I won't let you go.
昨日よりも 今よりも
More than yesterday, more than today,
また明日も 愛して
love me again tomorrow!
スッペシャル ジェネレーション
Special Generation!
Thank you so much, everybody! Thank you!
Thank you for coming! Thank you for watching!
Bye-bye!
One more! Ka-pow!
告知、告知！
Announcement, announcement!
小鳥遊キアラ誕生日記念グッズ2026！
Takanashi Kiara Birthday Merchandise 2026!
こちらがバナーです。
Here is the banner.
まず第一に、メインキャラクターとなる大きなアイテムは、抱き枕です！
First of all, the big item that is the main character is... body pillow!
何年もグッズを作ってきて、ついにやりました。
I finally did it after so many years of doing merchandise.
ちょっとネタ切れになってきたのかもしれないので…
I might be running out of ideas a little bit, so...
元々は絶対にやらないだろうなと思っていたことをやりました。
I did something that originally I never thought I would do.
KFP、私を放っておかないで。ベッドに寝かせておいてね、イェーイ！
KFP, don't leave me hanging. Leave me laying on the bed, yeah!
1つ目のアイテムはなんと！一生やらないと思ってたんですけど、
The first item is... a body pillow cover! I thought I'd never do this...
やっぱりここまで活動すると、もう出すしかなかった。抱き枕です！
but after being active for this long, I had to do it!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
次はとっても可愛いぬいぐるみセットです
Next, we have a really cute plushie set
私の愛猫たち、スムージーとチョンカーズ！
of my kitty cat babies! Smoothie and Chonkers!
とってもキュートでふわふわ、どこにでも連れて行けます
They're so cute and fluffy, and I can bring them everywhere now,
みんなもバッグや鍵につけることができますよ。
and you should too. You can hang them on your bag or keys.
2つ目のアイテムはそうですね、私の猫たちのぬいぐるみセットで、
The second item is a plushie set of my cats,
キーチェーンなどとして使えます。
which you can use as keychains.
え、どこにでも連れてってあげてください。
Please take them with you wherever you go.
次はこちらの缶バッジですが、今回は四角形なので、ちょっと珍しいです…
Next one is these badges, but they are a bit unusual because this time they are square...
…そしてフェイクレザー製なので、少し柔らかいです。
...and made from fake leather, so they are a bit squishy.
もちろん、これを使って痛バッグを作ることもできます。
And of course you can make an ita-bag with this, too.
今回のバッジはなんと、フェイクレザーで出来てますし、あと四角だし、
This time the badges are made of fake leather and are square,
変わっておりますが、もちろんこれでも痛バッグとかできたりしますよ。
which is unusual, but of course you can still make an ita-bag with them.
最後のアイテムは、KFPチキンをモデルにしたスマートフォンリングです。
Last item is the smartphone ring, modeled after KFP chickens.
これがあれば、羽でスマホを持つのもそんなに難しくなくなるかも？可愛い！
Maybe this way, holding your phones won't be as hard with your wings? Cute!
最後のアイテムはスマホリング！もちろんKFPモチーフです。
The last item is a phone ring! Of course, it's a KFP motif.
そしてそれ以外にも、ボイスパックがあります。
And besides that, there's also a voice pack.
ここ数ヶ月ボイスパックを出していなかったので、ぜひ手に入れてくださいね。激レアです！
I haven't been doing any voice packs these past months, so make sure to get this one. Rare!
そのほかには、久しぶりにボイスもあります。
Other than that, there's also a voice pack after a long time.
最近あんまり参加してないので、ぜひこの機会に、おねがいします！
I haven't done many lately, so please take this opportunity!
If you get the full set, then you receive a Polaroid from me alongside it,
and if you're lucky to get the limited one, then it will be signed by my own hands!
もちろん、いつも通りフルセットゲットすると、えー、チェキ、ついてきます！
Of course, as usual, if you get the full set, a Polaroid-style photo card comes with it!
限定版だとキアラのサイン入りですね！よろしくお願いします！
If it's the limited edition, it has Kiara's signature! Thank you for your support!
And one more thing before we end.
I have a super awesome song cover coming up right after this!
It's a collaboration with some cuties that might be familiar to you, IDJ!
Yay, IDJ!
このあとは、韓国のVTuberアイドル、IDJとのコラボ
After this, we will premiere a collab cover song with Korean VTuber idol IDJ,
歌ってみたプレミア公開しますので、見てください！
so please watch it!
I will try my best to raid you into it, but if it does not work out,
please make your way there on your own!
Besides that, thank you so much for celebrating my birthday today!
I worked so hard on this and I'm really proud.
Please leave a comment and a like, and if you can, get the merchandise!
In German we say: Auf Wiedersehen!
最後に、今日はお誕生日お祝いに来てくれて
Lastly, thank you so much for coming to celebrate
ありがとうございました！
my birthday today!
本当に、いろいろ努力してきたのです。
I really put a lot of effort into this.
コメントといいね、そしてもしよかったら
Please leave a comment, a like, and if you'd like,
グッズもよろしくお願いいたします！
check out the merch!
ではでは、Auf Wiedersehen!
Well then, Auf Wiedersehen!
See you in the song cover!